kshitiz saxena

designer/developer/programmer

EDUCATION

JAIPUR NATIONAL UNIVERSITY

Master's of Computer Application June 2017

RAJASTHAN UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Computer Application June 2012

RAJASTHAN BOARD

Senior Secondary April 2006

OBJECTIVE

I want to succeed in a stimulating and challenging environment, building the success of the company while I experience advancement opportunities.

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a designer, developer and programmer, specializing in webdevelopment, but with great interest to the AR/VR.

I am one of the very few self-driven and the fastest learner programmers with positive attitude. I will "NEVER SAY NO" to you. Somehow, I will find my way to do things.

EXPERIENCE

WEBCONTXT PVT. LTD. | LAL KOTHI, JAIPUR

Senior PHP Web Developer Dec 2016 - Dec 2018

GIRNARSOFT | JAGATPURA, JAIPUR

Front End Developer Nov 2015 - Dec 2016

SYON INFOMEDIA PVT. LTD. | JAIPUR AIRPORT, JAIPUR

Web Developer Mar 2014 - Nov 2015

LANGUAGE

English Hindi

INTERESTS

Creative Writing Audible books listening Traveling Cricket

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML5 95% CSS3 90% JavaScript 85% PHP 90% MySQL 80% WordPress 90% AngularJS 80% Node.js 80%

CONTACT

+91-9166332422

Near Gurjar Ki Thadi, Jaipur, Raj. - 302019 kshitizsaxena7@gmail.com